Guide to the Marshall P. Howard papers, 1890-1932
Howard, Marshall P. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Guide to the Marshall P. Howard papers 1890-1932.
3345
Marshall P. Howard
2 cubic ft.
Business and personal correspondence; account books; deeds; estate settlements and maps.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers consist of business and personal correspondence; account books; deeds; estate settlements; land and title searches with accompanying maps of areas in Tompkins, Allegheny, Broome, Cattaraugus, Schuyler and Wayne Counties. Includes material concerning the acquisition of lands for Allegheny State Park, Adirondack Park and the Connecticut Hill Fish and Game Refuge. Game refuge files contain deeds and papers pertaining to Cornell University.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Marshall P. Howard was a Binghamton, New York attorney and title examiner for the state attorney general, ca.1900 through ca.1920.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Papers consist of business and personal correspondence; account books; deeds; estate settlements; land and title searches with accompanying maps of areas in Tompkins, Allegheny, Broome, Cattaraugus, Schuyler and Wayne Counties. Includes material concerning the acquisition of lands for Allegheny State Park, Adirondack Park and the Connecticut Hill Fish and Game Refuge. Game refuge files contain deeds and papers pertaining to Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Howard, Marshall P.
Subjects:
Adirondack Park (N.Y.).; Allegheny State Park (N.Y.).; Connecticut Hill Fish and Game Refuge (N.Y.).; Estates (Law).; Land titles.; Land titles--Registration and transfer.; Parks--New York (State).; Title examinations.
Places:
Allegheny Co., N.Y.; Broome Co., N.Y.; Cattaraugus County (N.Y.); Schuyler County (N.Y.); Tompkins County (N.Y.); Wayne County (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Deeds.; Maps.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Allegany State Park (Title Examiner), ca. 1022-1931 (Box 1)
- Connecticut Hill Fish & Game Refuge (Title Examiner), ca. 1921-1931 (Box 1)
- Correspondence: business and personal, ca. 1905-1913 (Box 2)
- Adirondack Park: papers and maps (small bundle), ca. 1919 (Box 2)
- Estate of Jane Howard, Binghampton, Broome Co. (Executor), ca. 1901 (Box 2)
- Estate of Jarvis Howard, Town of Romulus, Seneca Co (Executor), ca. 1907 (Box 2)
- Wheaton: Kate M. Hotchkin against Frank M. Wheaton, et al., Broome Co., ca. 1905 (Box 2)
- Weeks and Davis: Frank W. Weeks, Charles A. Davis, Charles G. Blakeslee, bankrupt, Broome Co., ca. 1906 (Box 2)
- Winter: Sarah R. Winter, against Josephine Bellenger, et al., Broome Co., ca. 1900 (Box 2)
- Two or three cases unidentified, Broome Co., ca. 1900-1908 (Box 2)
- Account book: M.P. Howard as Executor of Jane Howard Estate, pages 16-29; M.P. Howard personal accounts, pages 30-139, ca. 1901-1910 (Box 2)
- Personal account book, ca. 1901-1910 (Box 2)